{
  "collection": {
    "name": "German - Czech - Ovoce",
    "description": "German - Czech - Ovoce",
    "hidden": "false"
  },
  "cards": [
    {
      "front": "Ananas",
      "back": "ananas",
      "urlOfFrontImg": "",
      "urlOfBackImg": "",
      "collectionId": 1,
      "collectionName": "German - Czech - Ovoce",
      "lastShow": null,
      "nextShow": "01-01-1970",
      "interval": 2,
      "hidden": "false",
      "dirty": "false",
      "ef": 2.5,
      "numberOfIteration": 1
    },
    {
      "front": "Apfel",
      "back": "jablko",
      "urlOfFrontImg": "",
      "urlOfBackImg": "",
      "collectionId": 1,
      "collectionName": "German - Czech - Ovoce",
      "lastShow": null,
      "nextShow": "01-01-1970",
      "interval": 2,
      "hidden": "false",
      "dirty": "false",
      "ef": 2.5,
      "numberOfIteration": 1
    },
    {
      "front": "Aprikose",
      "back": "meruňka",
      "urlOfFrontImg": "",
      "urlOfBackImg": "",
      "collectionId": 1,
      "collectionName": "German - Czech - Ovoce",
      "lastShow": null,
      "nextShow": "01-01-1970",
      "interval": 2,
      "hidden": "false",
      "dirty": "false",
      "ef": 2.5,
      "numberOfIteration": 1
    },
    {
      "front": "Banane",
      "back": "banán",
      "urlOfFrontImg": "",
      "urlOfBackImg": "",
      "collectionId": 1,
      "collectionName": "German - Czech - Ovoce",
      "lastShow": null,
      "nextShow": "01-01-1970",
      "interval": 2,
      "hidden": "false",
      "dirty": "false",
      "ef": 2.5,
      "numberOfIteration": 1
    },
    {
      "front": "Birne",
      "back": "hruška",
      "urlOfFrontImg": "",
      "urlOfBackImg": "",
      "collectionId": 1,
      "collectionName": "German - Czech - Ovoce",
      "lastShow": null,
      "nextShow": "01-01-1970",
      "interval": 2,
      "hidden": "false",
      "dirty": "false",
      "ef": 2.5,
      "numberOfIteration": 1
    },
    {
      "front": "Brombeere",
      "back": "ostružina",
      "urlOfFrontImg": "",
      "urlOfBackImg": "",
      "collectionId": 1,
      "collectionName": "German - Czech - Ovoce",
      "lastShow": null,
      "nextShow": "01-01-1970",
      "interval": 2,
      "hidden": "false",
      "dirty": "false",
      "ef": 2.5,
      "numberOfIteration": 1
    },
    {
      "front": "Erdbeere",
      "back": "jahoda",
      "urlOfFrontImg": "",
      "urlOfBackImg": "",
      "collectionId": 1,
      "collectionName": "German - Czech - Ovoce",
      "lastShow": null,
      "nextShow": "01-01-1970",
      "interval": 2,
      "hidden": "false",
      "dirty": "false",
      "ef": 2.5,
      "numberOfIteration": 1
    },
    {
      "front": "Himbeere",
      "back": "malina",
      "urlOfFrontImg": "",
      "urlOfBackImg": "",
      "collectionId": 1,
      "collectionName": "German - Czech - Ovoce",
      "lastShow": null,
      "nextShow": "01-01-1970",
      "interval": 2,
      "hidden": "false",
      "dirty": "false",
      "ef": 2.5,
      "numberOfIteration": 1
    },
    {
      "front": "Kirsche",
      "back": "třešeň",
      "urlOfFrontImg": "",
      "urlOfBackImg": "",
      "collectionId": 1,
      "collectionName": "German - Czech - Ovoce",
      "lastShow": null,
      "nextShow": "01-01-1970",
      "interval": 2,
      "hidden": "false",
      "dirty": "false",
      "ef": 2.5,
      "numberOfIteration": 1
    },
    {
      "front": "Orange",
      "back": "pomeranč",
      "urlOfFrontImg": "",
      "urlOfBackImg": "",
      "collectionId": 1,
      "collectionName": "German - Czech - Ovoce",
      "lastShow": null,
      "nextShow": "01-01-1970",
      "interval": 2,
      "hidden": "false",
      "dirty": "false",
      "ef": 2.5,
      "numberOfIteration": 1
    },
    {
      "front": "Pfirsich",
      "back": "broskev",
      "urlOfFrontImg": "",
      "urlOfBackImg": "",
      "collectionId": 1,
      "collectionName": "German - Czech - Ovoce",
      "lastShow": null,
      "nextShow": "01-01-1970",
      "interval": 2,
      "hidden": "false",
      "dirty": "false",
      "ef": 2.5,
      "numberOfIteration": 1
    },
    {
      "front": "Pflaume",
      "back": "bluma, slíva",
      "urlOfFrontImg": "",
      "urlOfBackImg": "",
      "collectionId": 1,
      "collectionName": "German - Czech - Ovoce",
      "lastShow": null,
      "nextShow": "01-01-1970",
      "interval": 2,
      "hidden": "false",
      "dirty": "false",
      "ef": 2.5,
      "numberOfIteration": 1
    },
    {
      "front": "Schalenfrucht",
      "back": "ořech",
      "urlOfFrontImg": "",
      "urlOfBackImg": "",
      "collectionId": 1,
      "collectionName": "German - Czech - Ovoce",
      "lastShow": null,
      "nextShow": "01-01-1970",
      "interval": 2,
      "hidden": "false",
      "dirty": "false",
      "ef": 2.5,
      "numberOfIteration": 1
    },
    {
      "front": "Zitrone",
      "back": "citrón, citron",
      "urlOfFrontImg": "",
      "urlOfBackImg": "",
      "collectionId": 1,
      "collectionName": "German - Czech - Ovoce",
      "lastShow": null,
      "nextShow": "01-01-1970",
      "interval": 2,
      "hidden": "false",
      "dirty": "false",
      "ef": 2.5,
      "numberOfIteration": 1
    }
  ],
  "settings": {
    "id": 1,
    "playVoiceText": "true",
    "languageOfVoice": "de",
    "typeOfVoice": "f2",
    "volumeOfVoice": 100,
    "displayAnswer": "false",
    "displayAnswerByRepeating": "false",
    "limitTAnswer": "false",
    "maximalAnswerTime": 60,
    "showAnswerTime": "false",
    "limitTAnswerByRepeating": "false",
    "maximalAnswerTimeByRepeating": 60,
    "showAnswerTimeByRepeating": "false",
    "filteringCards": "true"
  }
}
